Guide to the SPURS National Honor Society Records1922-2006
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- National Records, 4
  - Adams State Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Arizona State University Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Boise State College Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Brigham Young University Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Butler University Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - California Lutheran Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - California State College at Long Beach Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Central Washington State College Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Chico State College Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - College of Great Falls Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - College State College Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Colorado State University Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Eastern Montana College Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Eastern New Mexico University Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Eastern Washington State College Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Fort Wright College (Holy Names) Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Fort Hays Kansas State Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Fresno State College Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Humboldt State College Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Gonzaga University Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Idaho State University Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Illinois State University Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Jamestown College Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Kansas State Teachers College Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Kansas State University Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Kearney State College Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Linfield College Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Mankato State College Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Marylhurst College and Moorhead State College Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Montana State University Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - New Mexico Highlands University Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - New Mexico State University Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Northern Arizona University Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Membership List Cards (Box 35, Box 36, Box 37)
  - Membership List Cards (Box 39)
  - 50th Anniversary Registration Cards
  - Northern Montana College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Pacific Lutheran College Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Rocky Mountain College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - San Diego State College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - San Jose State Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Seattle University Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Southern Utah State Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Temple Buell College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - University of California at Los Angeles Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - University of Alaska Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - University of California at Santa Barbara Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - University of Colorado Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - University of Denver Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - University of Montana Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - University of Nevada, Las Vegas Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - University of New Mexico Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - University of the Pacific Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - University of Portland Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - University of Red Lands Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - University of Southern California Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - University of Texas at El Paso Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - University of Utah Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Utah State University Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Washington State University Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Western Montana State College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Whitman College Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Wichita State University Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - University of Wyoming Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Marsha Eichenauer, Region 8, Director Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Beverly Krivokapich, Region 9, Director Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Pam Walker, Region 10, Director Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Sue Kinder, Region 11, Director Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Maryanne Flynn, Region 1, Director Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Kathy Bailey, Region 2, Director Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Marsha Whalen, Region 3, Director Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Carol Stevenson, Region 4, Director Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Eileen Irvine, Region 5, Director Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Lucy Kaplan, National President Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Jane Palmer, National Vice President: PR Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Gale Buffam, National Vice President: Expansion Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Mary Virginia Kennedy, National Editor Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Mary Wierzbinski, Region 1, Director Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Karen Jean Peters, Region 2, Director Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Mary Hermann, Region 3, Director Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Ingrid Broten, Region 4, Correspondence Director, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Robyn Houston, Region 5 Correspondence, Director, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Chris Hiner, Region 5, Director Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Debbie Powell, Region 6, Director Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Jackie Wallace, Region 7, Director Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Mary Malmstone, Region 8, Director Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Karen Dill, Region9, Director Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Bobbie Burch, Region 4, Director Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Genette Hurst, Region 6, Director Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Barbara Bunyon, Region 7, Director Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Peggy Windnagel, Region 7, Director Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Roberta Davis, Region 8, Director Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Kittie Zittel, National President Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Gail Hanninen, Second Vice President Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Kathy Pautler, National First Vice President Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Tina Irani, National Editor Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Mary Clare, Stocking, Region 1, Director Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Helen, Black, Region 2, Director Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Judy Sutton, Region 3, Director Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Judy Payton, Region 4, Director Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Charlene Jackson, Region 5, Director Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Tita Marie Valdez, Region 6, Director Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Judy Barker, Region 1, Director Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - Randi Larango, Region 2, Director Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - Ruth Ann Lewis, Region 3, Director Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - Mada Petranovich, Region 4, Director Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Jill Kianu, Region 5, Director Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - Vicki Roehm, Region 6, Director Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Orona Palmer, First Vice President Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - Tixie Young, Second Vice President Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - Joyce Reichel, National President Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - Sonja Flatness, National Editor Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - Laura Henderson, Advisor Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - Laura Henderson Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - Blecha, Blanche Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Georgia Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Dunham, Joan Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Meyer, Joanna Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - (Cragon) Turley, Judy Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Jimenez, Dolores Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Barthels, Gwynne Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Larimore, Sheila Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - National Executive Council Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Executive Council Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Lyle, Corinne, President Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Ballenger, Ruth, Vice-President Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Anderson, Marilee, Director of Region 1 Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Lee, Zetta, Director of Region 2 Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Warnick, Grace, Editor Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Anacllerio, Sally, Direct of Region 3 Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2004 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Alumni Correspondence, 1971-1995 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Alumni Correspondence, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Alumni Response to Disbanding Correspondence, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Chapter Mailings Correspondence, 1995-2006 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Convention Correspondence, 1962-1976 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Convention Correspondence, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Convention Correspondence, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Convention Correspondence, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Disaffiliation Correspondence, 1961-2002 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Dissolution Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Spur Experiences of Various Individuals Correspondence (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Information on Old Spur Collections Correspondence (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Letters from Jessica Graham, Spur Founder Correspondence (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Martha Pearl "Teach" Jones Award Correspondence (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - National Officers Correspondence, 1972-1982 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter Information Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Taxes Correspondence, 2002-2006 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Greta's Correspondence, 1918 (Box 42A, Folder 1)
  - Fort Hayes and Expansion, 1964-1973 (Box 42A, Folder 2)
  - CWENS, 1958-1963 (Box 42A, Folder 3)
  - Region I, 1978 (Box 42A, Folder 4)
  - Region II, 1975-1976 (Box 42A, Folder 5)
  - Region III, 1963-1978 (Box 42A, Folder 6)
  - Region IV, 1963-1975 (Box 42A, Folder 7)
  - Region V, 1963-1975 (Box 42A, Folder 8)
  - Region VI, 1960-1971 (Box 42A, Folder 9)
  - Region VII, 1968-1978 (Box 42A, Folder 10)
  - Region VIII, 1978 (Box 42A, Folder 11)
  - Region IX, 1961-1978 (Box 42A, Folder 12)
  - Region X, 1964-1978 (Box 42A, Folder 13)
  - Region XI, 1960-1971 (Box 42A, Folder 14)
  - Region XI, 1963-1975 (Box 42A, Folder 15)
  - Boise State College, 1967-1971 (Box 42A, Folder 16)
  - Pacific University By-laws, 1982 (Box 42A, Folder 17)
  - Southern Utah State College, 1968-1971 (Box 42A, Folder 18)
  - National Project (Box 42A, Folder 19)
  - Membership Selection (Box 42A, Folder 20)
  - Junior Advisors (Box 42A, Folder 21)
  - Senior Advisors (Box 42A, Folder 22)
  - Service Projects (Box 42A, Folder 23)
  - Money Making Projects (Box 42A, Folder 24)
  - Fun Projects (Box 42A, Folder 25)
  - Founder's Day Activities (Box 42A, Folder 26)
  - Expansion Correspondence, Recent Years, 1978-1979 (Box 42A, Folder 27)
  - Budget (Box 42A, Folder 28)
  - Vice President Expansion Notebook (Box 42A, Folder 29)
  - Manual for Expansion Workshops (outdated) (Box 42A, Folder 30)
  - State of the Region, 1979-1982 (Box 42A, Folder 31)
  - Request for Information and Petitions (Box 42A, Folder 32)
  - Visitations - Chapters (Box 42A, Folder 33)
  - Big Sister Chapters (Box 42A, Folder 34)
  - Probation Communications (Box 42A, Folder 35)
  - Susan's Probation Correspondence, 1980 (Box 42A, Folder 36)
  - Expansion Workshops (Box 42A, Folder 37)
  - Expansion Reports (Box 42A, Folder 38)
  - National By-laws (Box 42A, Folder 39)
  - Inspuration (Box 42A, Folder 40)
  - Congratulations Letters, 1968; 1980 (Box 42A, Folder 41)
  - Possible People, 1963-1976 (Box 42A, Folder 42)
  - Memos to All Chapters, 1971-1975 (Box 42A, Folder 43)
  - Petitioning Information (Box 42A, Folder 44)
  - State of the Nation, 1976-1982 (Box 42A, Folder 45)
  - Regional Convention Invites (Box 42A, Folder 46)
  - Contact Lists - IAWS, 1965-1973 (Box 42A, Folder 47)
  - Regional Manuel and Report Forms (Box 42A, Folder 48)
  - Letters to the Regions Before Conventions (Box 42A, Folder 49)
  - Regional Conventions (Box 42A, Folder 50)
  - National Convention (Box 42A, Folder 51)
  - Convention Report Forms (Box 42A, Folder 52)
  - Convention Minutes (Box 42A, Folder 53)
  - Constitutions (Box 42A, Folder 54)
  - Expansion Letters to Chapters, 1972-1979 (Box 42A, Folder 55)
  - Awards and Certificates (Box 42A, Folder 56)
  - National Addresses (Box 42A, Folder 57)
  - National Spurs, 1979-1981 (Box 42A, Folder 58)
  - National Editor's Manual, 1979-1981 (Box 42A, Folder 59)
  - National Editor Manuel of Duties, 1981-1983 (Box 42A, Folder 60)
  - Membership Lists, Regions I-XI (Box 42A, Folder 61)
  - Old Membership List (Box 42A, Folder 62)
  - Orientation (Box 42A, Folder 63)
  - Archives (Old Papers) (Box 42A, Folder 64)
  - Visitations (Box 42A, Folder 65)
  - Traveling Information (Box 42A, Folder 66)
  - Probation People (Box 42A, Folder 67)
  - Chapter Officer Information (Box 42A, Folder 68)
  - Questionnaires (Box 42A, Folder 69)
  - Spur Newsletters - Regions (Box 42A, Folder 70)
- Audio and Photographic Materials, 5
  Items in this series document the visual and audio history of the Spurs. Objects include audiocassettes, audio reels, photographs, and 35 mm transparencies. Topics include conventions, meetings, Sur members, and Fang members.
  - First Business Meeting, Wahonal Spurs Convention, Bozeman, Montana Audiocassette, 1972 (Box 43)
  - Spur Slide Show Audiocassette, 1988
  - Spur Slide Show Audiocassette, 1988
  - Spur Song Audiocassette
  - Spurs (Old Slide Show) Audio Reel
  - Spurs Audio Reel
  - Wood Energy Institute West 5 PSAS Audio Reel, October 1986
  - Spurs (New Slide Show) Audio Reel, 1988
  - Thursday's two hour Business meeting Audio Reel, June 13, 1974
  - Friday Business Meeting Audio Reel
  - Saturday Business Meeting Audio Reel
  - #1 Spurs and Fangs Photograph, 1970-1971
  - #2 MSU Spurs and Fangs Photograph, 1973-1974
  - #3 Spurs Organized March Photograph, 1922
  - #4 Spurs First Active Group Photograph, 1923
  - #5 To Dean Paisley Photograph
  - Photographs #6-28 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - #6 Region 1 Convention, 1970
    - #7 Region 1 Convention, 1969
    - #8 Region 2 Convention, 1964
    - #9 Region 1 Convention, 1966
    - #10 Region 2 Convention, 1965
    - #11 Region 1 and 11 Convention, 1968
    - #12-13 Region 1 Convention, 1967
    - #14 Region 3 Convention, 1966
    - #15 Region 7 Convention, 1966
    - #16 Region 2 Convention, 1967
    - #17 Region 5 Convention, 1967
    - #18 Region 6 Convention, 1967
    - #19 Region 8 Convention, 1968
    - #20 Region 7 Convention, 1972
    - #21 Region 4 Convention, 1968
    - #22 Region 1 and 9 Convention, 1968
    - #23 Region 1 and 9 Convention, 1968
    - #24 Intermountain Convention, 1968
    - #25 Region 3 Convention, 1969
    - #26 Region 1 Convention, 1970
    - #27 Region 9 Convention, 1970
    - #28 Region 6 Convention, 1970
  - Photographs #29-52 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - #29-36 Spur Group Shot
    - #37 Spurs (MSC), 1924
    - #38 Washington State
    - #39 Wyoming Spurs
    - #40 Washington State, 1967
    - #41 Gonzaga University
    - #42 University of Redlands
    - #43 Pacific Lutheran University
    - #44 University of Wyoming
    - #45 Linfield Spurs, 1967
    - #46 Idaho State University
    - #47 Seattle University Spurs, 1967
    - #48 University of Idaho, 1967
    - #49 National Spurs Executive Council, 1968-1970
    - #50 MSU Chapter, 1967-1968
    - #51 MSU Spurs and Fangs, 1969
    - #52 MSC Spurs
  - Photographs #53-213 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - #53-70 Spurs
    - #71-86 Spurs
    - #87-102 Spurs
    - #103-120 Spurs
    - #121-137 Spurs
    - #138-155 Spurs
    - #156-170 Spurs
    - #171-190 Spurs
    - #191-213 Spurs
  - Photographs #214-256 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - #214-256 Spurs
  - Photographs #257-292 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - #257-292 Spurs, 1976-1977
  - Photographs #293-316 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - #293-316 Spurs 50th Anniversary
  - Transparencies #317-318 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - #317-318 FHSU, 1996-1997
  - Transparencies #319-435 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - #319-435 Golden Chain of Friendship
  - Transparencies #436-535 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - #436-535 Miscellaneous
  - Transparencies #536-619 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - #536-619 Miscellaneous
  - Transparencies #620-622 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - #620-622 Moorhead State University, 1993
  - Transparencies #623-645 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - #623-645 National Convention, 1972
  - Transparencies #646-684 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - #646-684 National Convention, 1975
  - Transparencies #685-724 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - #685-724 PASF National Officers, 1977-1978
  - Transparencies #725-738 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - #725-738 MSU Spur
  - Photographs #739-761 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - #739-761 MSU Spurs, 1989-1990
  - Photographs #762-791 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - #762-791 Spurs
  - Photographs #792-801 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - #792-801 Spurs, circa 1953-1975